General Reference; Collection ua950.002
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- M, 1872-2015; 13
  - Minerva, ca. 1967 July 16-1976 February 18 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - "Minerva in the Garden"by Ed Cowley, ca. 1996 December 2-2014 March 11 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Minority Assistance Program (MAP), ca. 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Minority Faculty Recruitment Project, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Minority Student Services, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Minority Students and U.A. History, Undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Mission Statement, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Mission Statement, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - The Mission Statement & Statement of Principle of the University at Albany State University of New York, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - "Mission Statement & Statement of Principle"of the University at Albany, SUNY, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Model Railroaders Club, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Model Schools, 1872 June-1899 June; Undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Modern Language Association, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Mohawk Campus, ca. 1972 February 2-1976 January 15 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Motion Picture About The State College, 1943 August (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Moving Up Day, 1927-1938 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Multicultural Awareness Program, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Multicultural Studies, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Mumford - The Lewis Mumford Center, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Municipal Finance Study Group, ca. 1972 August-1973 October (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Murphy, Alice Hastings Scholarship Fund, 1994 March 30 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Music Association, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Music Council, ca. 1941-1986 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Music, Department of, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Musical Performances, ca. 1897 December-1987 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Myren, Richard, ca. 1970-1977 May 3 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Myskania(Bernard Kerbel '33 on Meaning of Name), ca. 1917-1978 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Myskania "The Life and Death of Myskania"Alfred D. Basch '31, 1984 July (Box 23, Folder 63)
- N, 1851-2012; 14
  - Name Changes of the University, 1890 March 13-1984 August 30 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Named Buildings/Spaces, ca. 2012 December 7-2013 January 14 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Naming, ca. 1984 September 22-2012 December (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Nanotechnology, 2002 July 26-2005 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Nanotechnology, 2002 July 18-2005 April 24 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - National Association of Educational Secretaries, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - National Coalition Building Institute, 1999 January 8 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - National Collegiate Alcohol Awareness Week, 1998 October (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - National Defense Education Act Institute in English, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - National Teacher Corps, 1972 January 26 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - National Writing Project, 1991 September (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Native American Council, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Native American Pupils New York State Normal School See: Harriet T., 1851 November 27; 1993 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Natural History Lecture Series, 1981-1988 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - NEFER - ROHU(The Black Graduate and Professional Student Organization), Undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Nelson, L'Etat - C'est, 1960 September 21 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government, Undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Nemesis(Publication of the Feminist Alliance, successor to Athena), 1983; 1984 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - New Covenant Coffee House, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - New Democratic Coalition, ca. 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - New University Conference, Undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - New York Conference on Asian Studies, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - New York Educators Association, 1977 February-1978 October 3 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - New York Giants Training Camp, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - New York Giants Training Camp, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group, 1973 October 25-1985 April 15 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - New York State Citizen's Council, 1962 September (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - New York State Foundations of Education Association - "25th Anniversary Meeting", 1996 April 19-1996 April 20 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - New York State Department of Motor Vehicles, 1987-1990 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - New York State Newspaper Project, Undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - New York State Political Science Association, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - New York State Postmaster Annual Conference Commemorative Envelopes, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - New York State Teacher Association, Student Organization, 1971 October 12-1972 September 25 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - New York State Teachers Association, 1952 February 1-1961 January 10 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - New York State Teachers Retirement System, 1924 July 31-1967 September 1 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - New York State Theatre Institute, Undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - New York State United Teachers, 1973 April-1985 March (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - New York State Writers Institute, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Newman Association, 1971-1974 August 29 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Newman Club, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Newman Hall, 1918 October 3-1927 September 23 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Nonviolent Conflict Resolution Form, ca. 1970 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Normal Chart Rose - Marie Weber Paper, ca. 1994 May (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Normal School Chart by David Page, Undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Northeast Anthropological Association - Annual Meeting, 1988 March (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Northeast Document Conservation Center, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Northup Cluster(Freedom Quad), 1988 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- O, 1953-2012; 15
  - Off - Campus Association, ca. 1974 November 1-1984 May 6 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Off - Campus Association, ca. 1976 July 12 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Off - Campus Housing, ca. 1960 September-1984 September (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Off - Campus Housing, ca. 1984 December-1989 January (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Off - Campus Student Teaching, ca. 1953 August-1960 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Office for Research Report: Brain Power, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Omega Phi Beta Latino Sorority, Undated (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Omega Psi Phi Fraternity Pan Hellenic Council, Undated (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Omicron Delta Epsilon, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - "Once Upon A Time: Folklore and Fairytales in Children's Literature", 1997 March 14-1997 March 15 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - One Hundred Sixty - Eighth Graduating Class Commencement, 2012 May (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Opera Workshop, 1975 March 1-1976 November 7 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Organization Charts, 1959 October 20-1987 September (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Organizational Studies Program (Dept. of Management), 1987 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Orientation and Planning, Office of, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Office of Orientation, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Outcomes Assessment at Albany, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - "Outcomes Assessment at Albany"A Report to the University of New York, 1992 June (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Outfit, The, 1969 November (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Outing Club, 1973-1984 October (Box 24, Folder 4)
- P, 1844-2013; 16
  - Palestinian Rights, Capital District Committee For, 1982-1988 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Pan - Caribbean Association, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Parent Relations, Office of, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Parents' Weekend, 1957 March 16-1984 October 14 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Parents' Weekend, 1990-1991 October (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Patent Policy, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - PC Training Center, 1993 June (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Peace Corps Training Program Gift of Dewitt Ellingwood, ca. 1966 August 8-1966 September 1 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Peace Corps Training Program Gift of Dewitt Ellingwood, ca. 1966 August 29-1966 November 28 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Peace Institute, 1970 May 14-1970 September 4 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Peace Project, ca. 1974 September 19-1984 April 3 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Peace Studies, 1971 September 30-1973 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Pedagogue, 1959 April 6-1960 February 2 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - People and Food, 1984 September 25-1984 November (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - People for Socialism, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - People's Anti - Fascist Resistance League, ca. 1971 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - People's Party, 1972 May 2-1972 May 3 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Pep Band, 1978-1981 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Performing Arts Center, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Personnel - Budgeting Information System, 1974 October-1976 May (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Personnel, Office of, Undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Phi Alpha Theta, 1984 April 4-1991 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1974 March 7-1982 December 6 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Phi Beta Lambda, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Phi Beta Sigma Fraternity Mu Iota Chapter Pan Hellenic Council, Undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Phi Delta, 1990 June-1991 March (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1962 November 2-1984 March 24 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, Undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Phi Gamma Nu, 1974 January 17-1977 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma Fraternity Gamma Nu Chapter, recog. By Nat'l 1989 Interfraternity, Council (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Phi Sigma Sigma Sorority Delta Tau Chapter, recog, by national 1987 SUNYA Panhellenic Association of sororities (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Philological Society, Undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Philomathean Society, 1876 January-1891 June 16 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Philomathean Society Closing Exercises Memorabilia Picture for Women's Nights Exhibit, 1998 August 6 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Philosophy, Dept., 1990 March-1991 September (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Phobia and Anxiety Disorders Clinic, 1983 April-1988 September 26 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Physical Education, Department of, ca. 1954 June 30-1986 June (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Physical Education Building, 1968 February 28-1986 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Physical Plant, 1963-1971 April 19 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Physical Plant, 1971 April 27-1986 January 22 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Physical Plant Value, Original +2013, 2013 October 18 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Physics 230N (Department of Physics), 1990 June 25 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Physics Building, ca. 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Physics Building, James W. Corbett Laboratory, Physics 125 Physics Faculty, 1968-1994 April 25 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Physics Department, ca. 1993 January (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Physics Department, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Physics, Department of, Undated (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Physics, Department of, 1990 January 16-1991 January 22 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Pierce, Anna E. Oil Painting of, Gift of Class of 1927, 1926 July (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Pi Alpha Pi, Undated (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Pi Gamma Mu, 1966-2003 December 19 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Pi kappa Phi Fraternity Interfraternity Council, Undated (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Pi Lambda Phi Fraternity NY Kappa Alpha chapter, recog. By Nat'l 1985 Interfraternity Council (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Pi Omega Pi, 1960 April 1 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Pierce Hall Day Care Center see also Day Care Center, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Placement Office, Undated (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Placement Office, ca. 1971 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1969-1970 March 11 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Planning Office, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Planning Task Force, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Plays, 1920; Undated (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Policy on Smoking in Workplace, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Political Campaigns, ca. 1972 February 15-1976 October 18 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Political Economy Department, ca. 1971 March (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Political Science Association, 1971-1977 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - "Portrait of an Epoch: The Émigré Legacy"Conference, 1990 October 6 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Poverty Research and Training Program, 1974 November 20 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Pregnant and Parenting Teenage, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Edward Eldred Potter Alumni Room dedication Alumni House, 1997 October 18 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Potter Club(See also Potter, Edward Eldrod), ca. 1952-1981 October 3 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Potter Club Letterhead, Undated (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Potter, Edward Eldred, class of 1918 The Memoirs of by Cordella Rose Lackey, 1935 May 27 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Post Card Collection, Undated (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Pre - Health Professions Advisory Committee, 1984 September (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Pre - Law Society, ca. 1971-1975 April 16 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Pre - Med Pre - Dent Society, 1972-1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - President's Award for Excellence, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - President's Home 5 Englewood Place, Undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - President's House, 5 Englewood Place, ca. 1999 December 9 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - President's Medallion (see also Medallion of the University), 2003 February 12-2013 August 6 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Educational Publications of Principals and Presidents - State Normal School - State College For Teachers:1844 - 1959(Bibliography) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Portraits, Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Presidential School's Occasional Soiree Series, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Presidential Scholarship (Blank Form), 1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Scholars Program, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - President's Club, 1976 October 16-1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - President's Committee to Review Promotion and Continuing Appointment Policies, 1974 February (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - President's Lectureship Series, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Presidents and Principals of the University, ca. 1932 January 18-1978 May 23 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - President's Outstanding Young Alumni Service Award, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - President's Reception, 1970 June 6 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - President's Recognition Dinner (Gift of Sorrell Chesin), 1986 October 18-1998 January 19 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - President's Recognition Dinner, 1996 September 28-1998 October 24 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - President's Report, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - President's Task Force on Women's Safety, Undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Presidential Task Force on Priorities and Resources, SUNYA(Text of) Report of the, 1976 February 23 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - President's Undergraduate Leadership Awards, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - President's Undergraduate Leadership Awards, 1993 May 2 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Primer, Constitution, ca. 1958-1961 December 5 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Principles for the Ethical Conduct of Research and Scholarship, ca. 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Principles for a Just Community, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - "Principles of a Just Community", 1990 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Printing: Fundamental Principles of Correct Composition n, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Private Giving, Report of, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Private Support, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Prize International Cinema, ca. 1974 January 25-1980 April 18 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Professional Development Program (AIDS In - Service), 1991 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Professional Development Program - Programs, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - The Professional's Conference, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Profiles of the University, 1971 September-1976 April (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Profiles of the University, 1976 December-1979 December 18 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Program Development and Evaluation Department, ca. 1980-1984 January (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Program Development and Evaluation Department, 1984-1986 January 10 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Programs and Priorities, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Programs and Priorities, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Programs and Priorities Assessing a decade, 1980-1990 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Programs and Priorities, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Programs and Priorities, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Programs and Priorities, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Programs and Priorities, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Project Directors Guide, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Project Mercury, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Prokoviev Festival, 1922 April-1988 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Prominent Graduates, 1996-2005 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Promotion and Continuing Appointment Guidelines, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Promotion and Continuing Appointment Policies and Procedures, 1967 November-1974 March 15 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Promotion Review Panel, 1972 November 20 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Prospectus and Bulletin of Information, 1909-1910, 1909 April (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Prospectus For the University Center at Albany, 1973-1980, 1973 March 15-1973 June 1 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Prospectus For the University Center at Albany, 1975 July 31 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Protect Your Environment Club, ca. 1969 February 16-1976 March 11 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Protect Your Environment Club, ca. 1970 February-1973 November 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Protests and Demonstrations, ca. 1960 April 2-1977 December 27 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Psi Gamma Alumnae, 1909 June 8-1985 April (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Psychological Services Center, ca. 1981 September-1984 August (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Psychological Services Center, 1984 November-1991 September (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Psychology, Department of, 1886 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Psychology Society, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Public Administration, Department of, ca. 1969 June 6-1971 May 4 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Public Administration, Department of, 1972 January-1975 May 28 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Public Administration Department, 1976/05-1979/09/28 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Public Affairs, Graduate School, ca. 1971 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Public Administration Department, ca. 1982 November-1985 September (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Public Administration PAD 415+480 Course Descriptions, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Public Health, School of Fifth Anniversary Convocation, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - School of Public Health, 1990-1993 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Public Health School of: Faculty Research Directory, 1988 June (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Public Health, School of Infectious Disease, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Public History Program, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Public Service, Office of, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Public Officers Law, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Dept. of Public Safety, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Public Safety, Office of: Police/Safety, ca. 1986 November (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Public Service Training Program, Rockefeller College, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Public Service Training Program, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Public Service Training Program, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Public Safety - Traffic Division, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Public Services Office, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Publications Office, 1973 November 7-1983 May 9 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Puerto Rican, Latin American & Caribbean Studies, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Puerto Rican Organization for Liberation and Education, 1971 November 27-1973 March 3 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Puerto Rican Studies, Department of, 1971 May-1976 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Puerto Rican Studies, Department of, 1977 January 4-1986 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Puerto Rican Women, Interdisciplinary Guide for Research and Curriculum on, 1991 September (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Purchasing and Administrative Services, ca. 1966 January 21-1975 October 3 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Purchasing and Administrative Services, 1975 November 1-1991 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Purchasing Office, Printing Procedures, 1979 April-1983 September (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Purple, ca. 2007 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Purple and Gold, 1983 September-1985 April 21 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Q, 1990; 17
  - Q&A, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- R, 1918-2006; 18
  - Racial Concerns Across the Campus, Presidents Committee on Final Report, 1988 August 25 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Rabin, Yitzhak, ca. 1994 November 21-1995 December 6 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Racquetball Club, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Radiation Safety Committee, 1975 July-1991 September (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Radiation Safety Committee University at Albany, 1993 January (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Rank Among Colleges of State University College of Education at Albany, ca. 1960 November 28 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - "Raped & Sexually Assaulted, What You Can Do if You or a Friend is"SA Women's Issues Office + President's Task Force on Women's Safety, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Ratings, 1983 December (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Reading, Department of, ca. 1956 January 25-1991 September (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Reasonable Accommodation Policy, Statement on Americans With Disabilities Act, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Recitation Schedule, 1924-1927 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Recognition Dinner, 1985 October 5 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - V.F. Record Group Anelex, Undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Record and Registration, Office of, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Recreation and Convocation Center, ca. 1992 December 2 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Recruitment of Professional Employees, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Registrar, Office of the, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Register Office, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Rehabilitation Service, 1975 January 1 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Reid, William J., 2002 March 5 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Religious Activities, 1960 November 29-1962 December 18 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Religious Counseling, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Religious Holidays Law, 1966-1977 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Religious Studies Dept., 1991 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Religious Studies Program, 1984 March-1991 April 8 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Renaissance et Nouvelle Critique: Quatrieme Synopsisium sur la Renaissance: Modern Language of America, SUNYA Director: Raymond Hall, 1975 October 16-1975 October 19 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Report From the Health Survey, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - "Report if of Private Giving "Office of University Advancement, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Research Lectures, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Research, Office of: Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Research Involving Human Subjects, 1966 December 12-1972 March 1 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Research, Office for, ca. 1990 September 21-1991 September 24 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Research, Office of: Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Research - University At Albany "Albany Ranked Among Top Research Universities", Undated (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Reserve Officer Training Corps, 1973 August 23 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Residence Council Regulations, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Residence Halls Alumni Quad, ca. 1934 November-1986 April 19 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Residence Halls - Brubacher Hall, ca. 1950 January-1963 November 11 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Residence Halls: Empire Commons, 2002 September (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Residence Halls - Farrell House, 1942 March (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Residence Halls - Naming, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Residence Halls - Pierce Hall, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Residence Halls - Sayles Hall (Includes information on Alfred Trehanon '38 Room), ca. 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Residence Halls - SUNY Utilizations Study, 1984 September-1993 September (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Residence Halls - Syddum Hall, 1918-1952 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Residential Life, Department of, ca. 1993 May 14 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Residential Life & Housing, Department of, Undated (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Rethinking SUNY Report of the Board of Trustees of State University of New York, 1995 December 1 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Retired Senior Volunteer Program, 1974-1988 October 6 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Retirees from the University, 1965 May 15-1973 May 20 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Returning Students Association, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Returning Women Students, 1981 April (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Reunion Brunch, Undated (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Revisionist Zionist Alternative/Togar(RZA/Tagar), 1985 February (Box 27, Folder 57)